apps-builder.com 2015-06-07

# AppsBuilder - Privacy Statement

AppsBuilder Srl ("AppsBuilder," "we," or "us") knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by AppsBuilder when you use Apps-Builder.com and/or related AppsBuilder software and services (the "Service"), how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.Information We Collect

**User-Provided Information:** As part of using the Service, you may be required to provide certain information in order to register and set up an account (including billing and credit card information), or at your option for certain free Services (Registration Data). If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses. If you invite a friend to try AppsBuilder, we will use that friend's email address for the sole purpose of sending your invitation.

**Cookies Information:**

Cookies are small text files sent to the device of the user by the visited website. Cookies are stored in the computer hard disk, thus allowing the website to recognize user and store certain information concerning them, in order to permit or improve the service offered.

There are different types of cookies. Some are necessary to navigate on the site, others have a different purpose such as ensuring internal security, performing system administration tasks and statistical analysis, understanding which sections of the website are more relevant to users, or offering a personalized experience on the website. 

The Site uses cookies that do not run programs on the device of the user nor upload viruses on it, and that do not allow any kind of control over the device. AppsBuilder does not use cookies to access information on the device, to store data on it or to monitor the activities. The foregoing refers to both the device of the user or any other device used to access the Site.

Session cookies are stored temporarily on the device and are deleted when the user closes the browser. If a user registers to the site, AppsBuilder may use cookies to collect personal data that allow to identify the user during subsequent visits and facilitate access, login to the Site (for example by remembering username or nationality of the user) or the navigation on it. AppsBuilder also uses cookies for , system administration purposes, and to provide customized visits to the Site.

The Site may contain links to other sites. AppsBuilder has no access or control over cookies, web bacon and other tracking technologies used on third-party sites which the user may access from the Site, the availability of any content, and material that is published or obtained through such sites and related methods of treatment of the personal data; AppsBuilder expressly disclaims any responsibility accordingly. The user should check the privacy policy of third party websites accessed from the Site to learn about the conditions applicable to the processing of personal data since this Privacy Policy applies only to the Site as defined above. 

Disabling cookies may limit the ability to use the Site and prevent from benefitting in full of the features and services offered on the Site. In order to decide which cookies to accept or reject, please find below a description of the cookies used on the Site.

Types of cookies used 

  * First Party Cookies: First party cookies are set by the website visited by the user, whose address appears in the URL window.
  * Third Party Cookies: The third party cookies are set from a different domain than the one visited by the user. When a user visits a website and a different company sends the information through that website, that is a third party cookie.  
AppsBuilder has no access or control over cookies, web bacon and other tracking technologies used by third-party sites which the user may access from the AppsBuilder website in this regard expressly disclaims any responsibility accordingly. The user is encouraged to read the privacy policies of third party websites accessed through the Site, to understand the conditions applicable to the processing of personal data. 
  * Session Cookies: These cookies are stored temporarily and are deleted when the user closes the browser window. 
  * Persistent Cookies: Persistent cookies are stored on the device of the user between browser sessions, allowing the Site to remember preferences and actions on the Site. These cookies can be used for different purposes, e.g. to remember preferences and choices when using a site.
  * Essential cookies: These cookies are strictly necessary for the operation of the Site. Without the use of such cookies, some sections of the Site may not work. They include, for example, cookies that enable access to protected areas of the Site. These cookies do not collect personal information for marketing purposes and can not be disabled. Functional Cookies: These cookies are used to identify a user that returns to the Site. It allows to customize the content and remember preferences of the user (such as the language or country). These cookies do not collect information that can identify the user. All information collected is anonymous. 
  * Cookies for sharing on Social Networks: These cookies facilitate the sharing of site content through social networks such as Facebook and Twitter. To review the respective privacy policies cookies, you can visit the social networks websites. In the case of Facebook and Twitter please visit https://www.facebook.com/help/cookies and https://twitter.com/privacy.

How to change cookies settings  
Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but the user can usually change settings to disable this function. It is possible to block all types of cookies, or agree to receive only some of them disabling others. The "Options" or "Favorites" sections in the browser menu permit to accept or avoid receiving cookies and other tracking technologies, as well as to receive notification from the browser when these technologies are used. Alternatively, it is possible to manage cookies consulting the "Help" section of the toolbar present in most browsers. It is also possible to select the browser from the list below and follow the instructions: -Internet Explorer; - Chrome; - Safari; - Firefox; - Opera. From mobile:- Android; - Safari; - Windows Phone; - Blackberry. 

**File Information:** Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you view Apps-Builder.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

**Clear Gifs Information:** When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your AppsBuilder account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make AppsBuilder better for our users.

**How We Use Your Information**

**Automatically Recorded Information:** AppsBuilder does not claim any ownership in any of the content, including any text, data, information, images, photographs, music, sound, video or other material that you upload, transmit, store or otherwise make available in connection with the Service. Such content will remain your private information. AppsBuilder's servers will automatically scan and record certain information regarding your use of the Service, such as basic log information, your email address, and your IP address. Such automatically recorded information shall remain your private information and will not be made available to the public.

**User-Provided Information:** By providing AppsBuilder your email address you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. You may opt out or change the frequency of many Service-related communications by clicking an email preferences link provided at the end of every email AppsBuilder sends. As part of our registration process we may also ask your permission to use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may unsubscribe or change your mailing preferences by clicking a link that will appear at the end of all email communications. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers.  
AppsBuilder may use certain information about you without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, and maintaining security.  
We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; and (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.

**How We Share Your Information**

**Personally Identifiable Information:** AppsBuilder will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others and will not share it with others except as provided herein. AppsBuilder may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you. If we do this, such third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of AppsBuilder (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, AppsBuilder will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our License (http://www.Apps-Builder.com/legal/license), take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of AppsBuilder, our users or others.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain AppsBuilder services.

**How We Protect Your Information**

AppsBuilder uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to AppsBuilder and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, AppsBuilder makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

**Compromise of Personal Information**

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, AppsBuilder will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

**Your Choices About Your Information**

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information to AppsBuilder, in which case AppsBuilder will not be able to provide the Service to you. You can review and correct the information about you that AppsBuilder keeps on file by contacting us directly at [privacy@Apps-Builder.com](mailto:privacy@Apps-Builder.com).

**Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, AppsBuilder does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on AppsBuilder. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@Apps-Builder.com](mailto:privacy@Apps-Builder.com).

**Links to Other Web Sites**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including those that have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Notification Procedures**

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice or through conspicuous posting of such notice on our Website page, as determined by AppsBuilder in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Italian Based Service**

Our center of operation is in Italy. Your data is held in Italy and transactions are processed in Euros on servers in Italy. As such, all data is held in accordance with Italian laws and procedures which differ from those in other regions of the world. By using this service, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to these data policies.

www.apps-builder.com is currently hosted in Italy and Ireland. We may transfer and store your information gathered or submitted by you through the website, outside your country or outside the EEA. Though some countries do not provide an adequate level of data protection as defined under the Italian and European Laws on Privacy, we have taken steps to ensure that our hosting providers, provide the necessary level of protection for your information.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at [privacy@Apps-Builder.com](mailto:privacy@Apps-Builder.com), or send mail to:

AppsBuilder Srl  
Largo Francesco Richini, 2A  
Milan, Italy
